# **Paul Van**

Booragoon, WA, Perth, 6154 | 0452389408 | pavan192004@gmail.com

## Education

FEB 2023 - PRESENT

Bachelor of Advanced Science, Computing Major, Curtin University, Bentley, WA 6102

- Achieved a course weighted average of 76 for Semester 1 of 2024
- Achieved Course weighted average of 82.5 for semester 2 of 2023
- Achieved a course weighted average of 75.25 for Semester 1 of 2023

FEB 2016 - DEC 2022

High School Diploma (WACE certificate), High School Diploma (WACE certificate)

- Achieved ATAR of 98+ doing Mathematics Specs, Methods, Physics, Chemistry and English
- Achieved 80%+ for Specs, Methods, Physics and English in final WACE exam
- Achieved Distinction multiple times for CAT competition.

## **Employment history**

**JUNE 2024 - PRESENT** 

Warehouse Operations Associate, Amazon, Jankadot WA 6154, Perth

- Operate warehouse equipment safely, maintaining a clean and organized workspace.
- Eager to learn and apply new skills, committed to achieving team goals
- Finding optimal pathways/ routes to perform picking
- Shifts are 10 hours in length, experience with working long hours while maintaining quality of work

AUG 2022 - PRESENT

Private Tutor, Perth WA

- Design personalized lesson plans, helping students understand and comprehend material more completely.
- Offer the first 1 ~ 3 lessons free to build rapport with client and gauge student's abilities before charging to ensure client is getting what they are paid for.
- Tutored a range of years, from year 7 onwards to year 12.
- Tutored up to year 12 mathematics specialist, methods, physics and lower school chemistry.
- Tutors up to 6 to 10 students concurrently

#### FEB 2023 - DEC 2023

Kitchen Hand, MacDonalds, Melville Perth, WA

- Supported kitchen staff, ensuring timely meal preparation, and maintaining cleanliness.
- Handled customer orders efficiently, contributing to a positive dining experience.
- Collaborated with team members to improve service speed during peak hours.
- Efficiently managed customer orders and maintained high cleanliness standards at MacDonalds.

## Skills

- Proficiency in C, Python, Java and currently working with Kotlin and SQL in mySql.
- Proficient with Blender (3d hard-surface modelling and sculpting), texturing with substance painter and further modelling with marvelous designer and composition in photoshop
- Experienced with excel, word, powerpoint and general computer logistics
- As a private tutor, I have experience working with clients and building rapport while communicating clearly and succinctly
- Currently studying computer vision and 3d reconstruction as part of NPSC project

## Links

https://www.artstation.com/malamoots

## **About Me**

Fluent in speaking multiple languages: English, Cantonese and Chinese with a multicultural background growing up in Malaysia, Vietnam and currently based in Australia. These experiences helped me grow my people skills and to build rapport with people across many backgrounds. Timely, organized and reliable individual, able to collaborate with team members and students. Values fitness and physical health, big gym goer and run consistently to keep fit and active.

I love digital sculpting and 3d modelling, it requires dedication and discipline to see any artforms through, but the final render/sculpt is always worth the effort. Travelling and gaming are also fun past-times I enjoy. Finance, economics and investment are also fields in which I am extremely passionate and interested (even though it's not my major, having knowledge in those fields is always beneficial!).